

Laszlo Nagy

(+40) 740015554

Date of birth: 08/08/1997

Gender: Male

■ Email address: nagy.laszlo@aalto.fi

Website: https://laszlo-nagy.com/

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/laszlonagy97/

ABOUT ME

I am a software developer and student currently finishing my Master's Degree in **Cloud and Network Infrastructures** in the EIT Digital program. I have 2+ years of work experience in web development, working with a range of **full-stack** technologies. I like to be challenged often, to learn, and to improve.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

MSc in Cloud and Network Infrastructures

EIT Digital Master School [08/2020 - Current]

Address: Helsinki (Finland)

https://masterschool.eitdigital.eu/

Major: Cloud and Network Infrastructures
Minor: Innovation and Entrepreneurship
First-year: Aalto University - Helsinki, Finland
• Dean's incentive merit scholarship holder

o GPA: 4.23/5

Summer school with the topic of Digital platforms and smart cities

Second-year: University of Trento - Trento, Italy

Specialization: Beyond 5G

BSc in Computer Science

Babes-Bolyai University [09/2016 - 07/2019]

Address: Cluj-Napoca (Romania) https://www.ubbcluj.ro/ro/

- Erasmus+ 3rd semester at Charles University, Prague
- Erasmus+ 5th semester at Johannes Kepler Universitat, Linz

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web application developer

Freelance [06/2019 - 09/2021]

- Responsible for planning, tech architecture, delivery, and support for multiple projects which include features such as online auction, web-shop, presentation site with online payment, invoicing, and content management
- Technologies used: Laravel PHP, MySQL, Vue.js, Redis, SocketIO, Docker, AWS
- Used *Trello, Asana* for project management, drafted and negotiated contracts with clients based on requirements engineering

Web Developer Intern

Lynx Solutions [06/2018 - 08/2018]

City: Cluj-Napoca Country: Romania

- Designed and developed a web application API for a large user base
- Managed CI/CD pipelines, staging and production environments
- Worked with Laravel PHP, Node.js, SocketIO, Angular frameworks

DIGITAL SKILLS

Web Development

PHP Laravel / SQL (MySQL) / Node.js, Vue and Angular / CSS & Sass (+Bootstrap & TailwindCSS) / RESTful api

Software engineering

Cloud platform: AWS, GCP etc. / Linux system programming / Java, C, C++, C#, Python / Git / Vagrant / Docker

Other

Microsoft Office / Atlassian Confluence and Jira / Basic Figma / Adobe Creative Suite / Trello, Asana, Slack, Notion

HONOURS AND AWARDS

Intelligence in Software section winners

HackTGM [2017]

Won the prize of "Intelligence in Software" at the HackTGM Hackathon with my colleagues. Later we collaborated with one of the partner companies to bring the product idea to life, kicking off my journey into web development.

https://devpost.com/software/voluntapp

PROJECTS

Automated Vagrant Network Deployment

Python-based script that generates a Vagrant configuration file based on user input to create a network topology with virtual machines, switches, and routers with configurable bandwidth and network delay.

https://github.com/nlacko97/automated-vagrant-network-deployment

Real-time whiteboard protocol

Whiteboard application where users can interact in real-time. Features include drawing, sticky notes, image upload, and many others. Implemented with NodeJS and SocketIO.

https://github.com/nlacko97/collaborative-whiteboard

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **Hungarian** | **Romanian**

Other language(s):

English German

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2 LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2 SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2